回顾第四课，我们学到了
Back in lesson four, we learned that the
Android·运行时会杀掉不可见的activity
Android Runtime will kill apps with no visible activities,
来给前台可见的应用释放资源
in order to free resources needed by the foreground
但是，如果我们的应用即使在不可见时
app. But what if your app has tasks that
也需要继续任务呢？
need to continue when the activity isn't visible, things
比如下载文件，上传照片，播放音乐
like downloading files, uploading photos, or playing music? Well,
有一个应用程序的组件就是为这种情况而生的——Services
there's an application component for that. Services. We've already
我们已经介绍了activity,content provider,broadcast
introduced Activities, Content Providers,
recriver还有intent。
Broadcast Receivers and Intents. Services,
Service（服务）就是Android组件的最后一部分
are the final piece to the Android app component
开始一个服务像极了activity，
puzzle. You start services much like you do activities, by
为startService方法传递一个intent参数就行了
passing in an intent to a Start Service call.
你也可以用同样的办法停止它
And you can stop services the same way, by calling
调用stopService方法，传入你想停止的服务的名字
Stop Service and passing in the name of the
不同于activity,服务没有用户界面
service you want to stop. Unlike activities, services have no
他们运行时，比后台activity有更高的优先级
user interface and they run at a higher priority than
这就意味着运行着服务的应用程序
background activities. This means that an app with a running
很少在运行时
service is less likely to be killed by the run
为了释放资源给前台可见activity而被杀掉
time, in order to free resources for the foreground activities.
实际上，如果服务在应用内部停止它之前
In fact, by default, the system will attempt to restart
就被中断的话，系统默认会重启这个服务
services that are terminated before they are stopped from within
这是它简单的生命周期的映射。
the app. This is reflected in this simplified life cycle.
和activity相比，服务被设计成一个用来执行长时间操作的
Compared to Activities, Services are designed to execute longer running
不应被中断的任务。通常，你只需要
tasks that shouldn't be interrupted. Typically, you'll only need to
重写onStartCommad方法，这是你希望执行后台任务的地方
override the onStartCommad handler, which is where you begin the background
但是请注意
task you wish to execute. But notice that there are
并不存在一个可覆盖的方法，来监控应用状态的改变，从而反映
no handlers for monitoring changes in state, to reflect the
应用是否被移到后台去了。这是因为
app moving to the background. This is because the running
运行中的服务自己给framework层发送了一个信号
service itself sends a signal to the framework that the
指出这个运行了服务的应用应该比
containing app should be considered higher priority than other apps
其他后台未运行服务的程序拥有更高优先级
in the background that don't have running services. In some
一些情况下，你的服务可能执行一个没有交互界面的任务
cases your service may performing a task, that while not
没有用户操作的话不能被中断
having UI, can't be interrupted without interfering with the user experience.
比如，播放音乐或者汽车导航
For example, playing music or helping with in car
这些情况下，你的服务应该
navigation. In these cases, you can indicate that your
通过调用startForeground
server should be considered to be running in the
来声明它要运行在前台。你会注意到这个调用是在通知里完成的
foreground by calling startForeground. You'll notice that this call takes
这将会被一直显示，不能取消
in a notification. This will be displayed, and can't
直到任务停止或者你调用 stopForeground方法
be dismissed until the service has stopped, or you
后面你会跟着Dan学到更多关于通知的部分
call stopForeground. You'll learn more about notifications a little
但现在，记住前台服务和前台activity有
later, with Dan. But for now, note that a foreground
同样的优先级就好了
service runs at the same priority as a foreground
这会使得它不可能被运行时引擎
activity. Making it nearly impossible for the run time
为了释放更多的资源而杀掉
to kill in order to free resources. Now, you
现在你可能会考虑，我可以用生命周期
may be thinking to yourself, I could save a lot
保持一些麻烦的处理，只创建长时间运行，
of trouble dealing with life cycles, just by creating
或者前台服务就好了
long running, or even foreground services. Well, I grew up
嗯...我生长在澳大利亚的海滨，所以
along the coast in Australia, so I learned young
我自小就明白了逆着潮流游泳既费力而且最终都是徒劳。
that swimming against the current is exhausting and ultimately futile.
这种情况下，意味着会让系统管理资源变得
In this case, that means making it more difficult
更加困难，最后导致
for the system to manage resources, ultimately leading to a
更差的用户体验。顺着潮流游泳。
worse user experience. Swim with the current. Use foreground
前台服务只在绝对需要的时候才运行
services only when and for as long as absolutely necessary,
并且在不需要的时候要尽快关闭它
and stop all services as quickly as possible. It's
注意，就像activity和receiver一样，服务同样运行在主线程
also important to note that like activities and receivers, services
所以你需要
run on the main thread. So you'll need to
用后台线程或者异步任务来执行
use a background thread or a sync task to execute
你希望在服务里处理的长时间运行的任务
the long running tasks you wish to do
为了简单
within your service. To make life easier, you can
你可以使用intent service类
use the intent service class. Which implements the most
它实现了最通用的实践模式
common best practice pattern, for using intents, which are
来在服务里使用intent。它创建了一个intent队列
executed within a service. It creates a queue of
传入的intent在startService被调用时入队
incoming intents, passed in when start service is called.
这样，在你的IntentService实现类中的onHandleIntent方法里
These are then, processed sequentially on a background thread,
这些intent就在后台线程中按顺序一一执行了
within the onHandleIntent handler, within your intent service implementation.
当是队列空了的时候，服务自己会终止
When the queue is empty the service self terminates
直到接收到新的intent，进程才再次开启
until a new intent is received and the process begins
服务是一个强大的工具
again. Services are a powerful tool and it's important
理解怎么运用好它们是很重要的
to understand how you can use them but in practice
但是在实践中，总会有一个可选的开发框架来替换你自己的
there's often a framework alternative to rolling your own
服务实现。不管它是一个后台任务的intent service
service implementation. Whether that be an intent service for executing
还是一个你将在后面学到的同步适配器
background tasks or the sync adapter which you'll learn about
它可以完美地执行后台数据同步
later in this lesson. Perfect for performing background data synchronization